PEDRO MEDINA ROBLES

COMPUTER SYSTEMS ENGINEER

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATE: 13260429

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

BACKEND

- PHP (LARAVEL)
- PYTHON
- NODE.JS
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB

FRONT-END

- ANGULAR
- jQuery
- React.js
- RXJS
- NGRX

Tecnical Skills

- GIT
- AZURE DEVOPS
- KANBAN
- SCRUM
- API-REST
- Linux
- Windows

PERSONAL SKILLS

- CREATIVE
- RESULTS ORIENTED TENACIOUS
- PATIENT

CONTACT

9371678906 pedro.medina.ro97@outlook.com Col. Tascoob Street River Mezcalapa Block 3 #8 CP.86500, H.Cárdenas, Tabasco

GitHub; PedroMedina97





EDUCATION

COMPUTER SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

University of the Valley of Mexico | 2016 - 2021

Languages

English B2 conversational

COURSES | TRAININGS

BOOTSTRAP

PHP

JAVASCRIPT, NODE JS, ANGULAR, JQUERY

ABOUT ME

Computer systems engineer with experience in full-stack web development. I have worked on projects in the medical, automotive, agricultural and financial sectors, implementing technologies such as Node.js, Laravel, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Angular, jQuery, REDUX Patterns and Javascript-based technologies, in addition to having knowledge in other programming languages.

EXPERIENCE

PROFESSIONAL CONSULTANT SERVICES

NTTDATA - CITI | JULY, 2024 - OCTOBER, 2024 (PARTIAL)

Web Programmer for temporary project with CITI-BANAMEX, as a client of NTTDATA

Applied Technologies:

Angular, Bootstrap, Node.js, API-REST

Tools:

Jira, GIT, SCRUM, KANBAN

WEB DEVELOPER

KOUD | August. 2023 - NOVEMBER. 2024

Web developer for software developer in which I was involved in several corporate projects for KOUD's clients:

Automotive Sector:

Project with Dalton corporate for buying and selling cars.

technologies:

Angular, Bootstrap, Material Design, JWT, Node.JS, API-REST MongoDB, RXJS. NGRX

Agricultural Sector:

Project for a company in the agricultural sector of geo-positioning and measurement of crop quality through maps and geojson.

technologies:

Angular, Bootstrap, JWT, Angular, Node. js, MongoDB, API-REST, Mapbox

ERP project for leasing company implementing CxC, CxP, Treasury, Invoicing modules, migration of old system in PHP LARAVEL to Node.js

Applied Technologies:

Angular, Materialize.css, JWT, Laravel, PostgreSQL, Node.js, MongoDB, API-REST Tools:

SCRUM, KANBAN, GIT, AZURE DEVOPS

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING ASSISTANT

IPS GROUP | FEBRUARY. 2022 - MARCH. 2023

Software Engineering Assistant for Internal ERP of a corporate business in the oil sector, support to face-to-face and remote users:

applied technologies:

Angular, jQuery, Bootstrap, JWT, PHP (LARAVEL), API-REST, MySQL.

Tools:

SCRUM, KANBAN, JIRA, GIT, VS CODE.

PROJECT LEADER / JUNIOR PROGRAMMER

Xinergia Group | NOVEMBER 2019 - JANUARY. 2022

Technical leader of ERP project for customer and company management of the corporate network of the health sector, process improvements and migration to JavaScript-based technology.

applied technologies:

Angular, Node.js, MongoDB, JWT, API-REST, Payments, Billing, Bootstrap, Laravel, MySQL.

Tools:

SCRUM, KANBAN, MS Project, Git, VS CODE